Indiana University Division of Biological Sciences records, 1906-1988 C85
Indiana University Archives
- Subject Files
  - Library (Box 8)
    - Library Committee Reports, 1973-1977 (Box 8)
    - DBS-Library (Box 8)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 8)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 8)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 8)
    - Jordan Hall Addition, 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - Lilly Library, 1963-1966; undated (Box 8)
  - List of Books in Seminar Room, 1970; undated (Box 8)
  - List of Faculty Publications by Department, 1950-1971; undated (Box 8)
  - Long, J.A., 1938-1950 (Box 8)
  - "M", 1927-1954; undated (Box 8)
  - M-Q, 1973-1977 (Box 8)
  - Mack, John, 1961; undated (Box 8)
  - M.A. Exams, 1960-1970; undated (Box 8)
  - Marine Biological Laboratory-Woods Hole, Mass., 1924-1940 (Box 8)
  - Marine Mammals-FAO Expert Consultation Project-Bergen, Norway, Sept. 1976, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
  - Marine Sciences And Related Fields, 1970 (Box 8)
  - Master Faculty Cards, 1971-1973; undated (Box 8)
  - M.A.T. (Box 8)
    - 1967-1972, undated (Box 8)
    - 1977 (Box 8)
    - Program, 1972-1976 (Box 8)
    - Brochure 3/73, 1973; undated (Box 8)
    - Committee (Biology)-Old File, 1969-1977 (Box 8)
  - Mc, undated (Box 8)
  - McClung, L.S., undated (Box 8)
  - McDonald, Betty, undated (Box 8)
  - Medical Genetics, 1962; undated (Box 8)
  - DBS-Medical School Relations, 1976-1977 (Box 8)
  - Medical School Relations File, Prior to Sept.1965, 1960-1965 (Box 8)
  - DBS-Medical Sciences Program, 1965-1969; undated (Box 9)
    Previously: Combined Degree Program
  - Medical Science Program (Box 9)
    - 1st Semester, 1970-1971 (Box 9)
    - 2nd Semester, 1970-1971 (Box 9)
    - Basic Data, 1971; undated (Box 9)
  - Medical Sciences Situation, 1974-1975 (Box 9)
  - Memorandum (Box 9)
    - 1967 (Box 9)
    - 1968 (Box 9)
    - 1970 (Box 9)
    - 1971 (Box 9)
    - 1972 (Box 9)
    - 1973 (Box 9)
    - 1974 (Box 9)
    - 1975 (Box 9)
    - 1976 (Box 9)
  - Metz, C.W., 1931-1946; undated (Box 9)
  - Micro Faculty Meeting Minutes (Box 9)
    - 1959-1962 (Box 9)
    - 1963-1967 (Box 9)
    - 1968-1972 (Box 9)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 9)
    - 1975-1977 (Box 9)
  - Microbiology (Box 9)
    - Degrees-Statistical and Alumni Information, 1942-1976 (Box 9)
    - Departmental Memos, 1974-1976 (Box 9)
    - Journal Club, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Laboratory Implementation Program-L.S. McClung, 1976-1977; undated (Box 9)
    - Majors, 1978-1983 (Box 9)
    - Memos To Faculty, 1972-1976 (Box 9)
  - Minnick, D.E., 1927-1953 (Box 9)
  - Minority Student Recruitment, 1975; undated (Box 9)
  - Molecular And Cellular Biology (Box 9)
    - Minor, 31 Jan 1977 (Box 9)
    - Training Grant, 1975-1976; undated (Box 9)
  - Monroe Reservoir (Box 9)
    - Biological Station, 1965-1968; undated (Box 9)
    - Field Station Building, 1965-1968; undated (Box 9)
    - Field Station (Water Resources Research Center), 1964-1974; undated (Box 9)
    - Director, 1965-1966 (Box 9)
  - DBS-Morrison Hall, 1965-1973; undated (Box 9)
  - Mucia/ Midwest University Consortium For International Activities, 1972-1975; undated (Box 9)
  - Mucia (Venezuela), undated (Box 9)
  - Muller, Hermann J., 1945-1955; undated (Box 9)
  - Muller Reprint Collection, 1967-1974; undated (Box 10)
  - "N", 1936-1953 (Box 10)
  - NASA, 1965-1966, undated (Box 10)
  - National Center For Biological Education-CUEBS Project, 1970 (Box 10)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF) (Box 10)
    - 1968-1975, undated (Box 10)
    - 1966-1974, undated (Box 10)
    - Research Participation High School- Teachers, 1960-1961 (Box 10)
  - NDEA Title IV (Box 10)
    - 1964-1970, undated (Box 10)
    - Fellowships, 1966-1971; undated (Box 10)
  - Neumann, G.K., 1942; undated (Box 10)
  - New Course Requests, 1967-1976; undated (Box 10)
  - New Faculty Positions Requested For 1967-1968 (Box 10)
  - News Bureau, 1971-1972; undated (Box 10)
  - Newsletter-Dept. Of (Box 10)
    - Bacteriology, 1957 (Box 10)
    - Biology, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1966-1967; undated (Box 10)
  - Noland, Lowell E., 1949-1950 (Box 10)
  - Nominations For Divisional Committees, 1970-1971; undated (Box 10)
  - NSF (Box 10)
    - Fellowships, 1966-1977; undated (Box 10)
    - Grants, 1972 (Box 10)
    - Projects, 29 Nov 1982 (Box 10)
  - N (Miscellaneous), 1976; undated (Box 10)
  - "O", 1931-1964 (Box 10)
  - Ogles, Tom, 1976 (Box 10)
  - Open House, undated (Box 10)
  - Open House-Zoology Department, 1937-1938 (Box 10)
  - "P", 1921-1949; undated (Box 10)
  - Patient Policies, undated (Box 10)
  - Payne, Fernandus, 1946 (Box 10)
  - Payne Portrait, 1924; 1961; undated (Box 10)
  - Personnel Division Bulletins, 1947-1964; undated (Box 10)
  - Pest Control, 1972 (Box 10)
  - Ph.D. Dissertation Requirements, 1971-1976; undated (Box 10)
  - Philips 300 Electron Microscope Information, 1966-1969; undated (Box 10)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 10)
  - Physical Instruments Committee, undated (Box 10)
  - Physical Plant, 1973-1976; undated (Box 10)
  - Plant Sciences, 1973-1975; undated (Box 10)
  - Policy Committee, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Political Activities, 1970 (Box 10)
  - Positions (Various Colleges), 1947 (Box 10)
  - Postdoctoral Appointments, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Poynter Center, 1973-1974; undated (Box 10)
  - Preparatory Studies Program, 1976 (Box 10)
  - Principa Press, 1933-1947; undated (Box 10)
  - Professional Activities (Box 10)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 10)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Professional Activities Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - Professional Practice Program In Microbiology, 1973; undated (Box 10)
  - Program Steering Committee, 26 Jan 1977 (Box 10)
  - Promotion Procedures, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
  - Promotion and Tenure (Informative), 1974-1984 (Box 10)
  - Publications-Mossholder, 1954-1955 (Box 11)
  - Purchasing Department, 1939-1964 (Box 11)
  - Purchasing, Memos, 1976-1977 (Box 11)
  - Purdue Univ., Collaborated Research, 1941; undated (Box 11)
  - Putnam, Frank W., 1964-1965; undated (Box 11)
  - "Q", 1917-1936; undated (Box 11)
  - Quotations, 1937-1948; undated (Box 11)
  - "R" (Box 11)
    - 1926-1949 (Box 11)
    - 1950-1954 (Box 11)
  - R-V, 1975-1977 (Box 11)
  - Radiation-Safety, 1974 (Box 11)
  - Radioisotopes And Radiochromatogram, undated (Box 11)
  - Radiological Control Committee (Box 11)
    - 1962-1964, undated (Box 11)
    - 1956-1963 (Box 11)
  - Radiological Health Survey Reports, undated (Box 11)
  - Radiological Safety Committee (Radiation Regulations-Draft), 1961-1962; undated (Box 11)
  - Reagan, Franklin Pearce (A. B. 1913; Assoc. Prof. of Anatomy, 1927-1929), 1920-1936 (Box 11)
  - Real Estate- Eigenmann Kinsey Davis, Moenkhaus-Restrictive Deed, 1986; undated (Box 11)
  - Recommendation Guidelines, 1981 July 20 (Box 11)
  - Recruitment (Box 11)
    - 1971-1976, undated (Box 11)
    - 1972-1973, undated (Box 11)
  - Regional Campuses-General, 1962-1968; undated (Box 11)
  - Registration, 1979-1981 (Box 11)
  - Remodeling, 1967-1975; undated (Box 11)
  - Remodeling Of Jordan Hall, undated (Box 11)
  - DBS-Renovations and Remodeling (Box 11)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 11)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 11)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 11)
    - Old File, 1968-1973; undated (Box 11)
  - Replies To Salary Questionnaire, 1970 (Box 11)
  - Reports On Educational Policies Committee (EPC) Meetings (Box 11)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 11)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 11)
  - Reports On Executive Committee meetings, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Report: Review of DBS, undated (Box 11)
  - Requests For Faculty Additions-Departmental, 1965-1967 (Box 11)
  - Research Publications, 1983 Aug 25 (Box 11)
  - Research And Development Deanship (Search and Screen Committee), 1976 (Box 11)
  - DBA-Research and Training Grant Summary, 1966-1968; undated (Box 11)
  - Revised Organization of the Division of Biological Sciences, 1962-1965 (Box 11)
  - Rice, Edward L., 1926-1947 (Box 12)
  - Richards, A., 1911-1942 (Box 12)
  - Ricker, W.E., 1938-1951; undated (Box 12)
  - Riddle, Oscar, 1921-1948 (Box 12)
  - Roberts, Elmer, 1932-1943 (Box 12)
  - Roberts, William M., 1973-1974 (Box 12)
  - Robinson, Arthur, 1927-1947 (Box 12)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1934-1947 (Box 12)
  - Roggers, G.G., 1930-1939 (Box 12)
  - DBS-Room Inventory, 1970; undated (Box 12)
  - Runner, Meredith N., 1937-1952 (Box 12)
  - Ryan, Irene-Order Librarian, 1926-1949 (Box 12)
  - "S" (Box 12)
    - 1921-1948, undated (Box 12)
    - 1925-1954, undated (Box 12)
  - Safe Laboratory Procedures: "Guide" For Radiation and Radioactive Materials, undated (Box 12)
  - Safety, 1972; 1982 (Box 12)
  - Safety Division, 1951-1952 (Box 12)
  - Saila, Saul B., 1951; undated (Box 12)
  - Salary Inequities (Box 12)
    - (DBS Faculty), 1974 (Box 12)
    - 1975 (Box 12)
  - Salary Roll, October 26, 1925 (Box 12)
  - Search Committee, 1973-1983; undated (Box 12)
  - Seminar, 1979-1985; undated (Box 12)
  - Schaffner, Joseph C., 1951-1963; undated (Box 12)
  - Schedule of classes, 1955-1963 (Box 12)
  - Scholarships, etc., 1962-1968 (Box 12)
  - Schooley, J.P., 1926-1945 (Box 12)
  - Science Advisory Committee (Box 12)
    - 1965-1966, undated (Box 12)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 12)
    - General, 1963; (2 folders) (Box 12)
    - Minutes, 1968-1971; 1974 (Box 12)
  - Scott, Will (Inst. Prof of Zoology, 1908-1937), 1911-1940; undated (Box 12)
  - Shoemaker, Hurst, 1934-1938 (Box 12)
  - Sinnett, David B., 1961 (Box 12)
  - Smith (Miscellaneous), 1919-1944 (Box 12)
  - Simmons, Eric L., 1939-1947 (Box 12)
  - Sonneborn, Tracy M., 1938-1950; undated (Box 12)
  - Spencer Lens Company, 1927-1943 (Box 12)
  - Spieth, Herman T., 1926-1947 (Box 12)
  - Spratt Jr., Nelson T., 1950-1951; undated (Box 12)
  - DBS Stockroom and Services Consolidation (Box 12)
    - 1973-1975, undated (Box 12)
    - 1970-1973, undated (Box 12)
  - Stone (Miscellaneous), 1928-1938; undated (Box 12)
  - Stout, S.E., 1931-1942; undated (Box 12)
  - Streightoff, Frank H., 1926-1931 (Box 12)
  - Summer Session (Box 12)
    - Budget, Faculty Courses Offered, etc., 1963-1966 (Box 12)
    - H.B. Allman, 1947-1963; undated (Box 12)
    - 1967 (Box 12)
    - 1968 (Box 13)
    - 1969 (Box 13)
    - 1975 (Box 13)
    - 1976 (Box 13)
  - Support-High School Teachers Institute (Biology), 1964 (Box 13)
  - Summer Teaching Appointments, 1978 (Box 13)
  - S (Miscellaneous), 1976-1977; undated (Box 13)
  - "T", 1916-1962 (Box 13)
  - Teaching, 1977; 1982 (Box 13)
  - Teaching Awards, 1969-1970; undated (Box 13)
  - DBS-10 Year Proposal (Hirs), 1970-1971 (Box 13)
  - Textbook Orders, 1959-1976 (Box 13)
  - Thefts, 1973 (Box 13)
  - Thorwaldson, Thorberg-Correspondence, 1916-27 (Box 13)
  - Transportation Revolving Fund, 1971 (Box 13)
  - Treasure's Office, 1948-1955 (Box 13)
  - Turner, C.L., 1934-1942 (Box 13)
  - Tyler, David B., 1970-1972 (Box 13)
  - T (Miscellaneous), 1975-1977 (Box 13)
  - "U", undated (Box 13)
  - UEPC, 1972 (Box 13)
    - Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - Undergraduate (Box 13)
    - General, 1982 (Box 13)
    - Problems and Decisions, undated (Box 13)
  - University Committee, 1958; undated (Box 13)
  - University Division (Advisory), 1971-1972 (Box 13)
  - U.S. Army Grants, 1953-1964; undated (Box 13)
  - U.S. Public Health Grants, 1947-1950 (Box 13)
  - U (Miscellaneous), 1976 (Box 13)
  - "V", 1926-1954 (Box 13)
  - Van Epps, R.E., 1976-1977 (Box 13)
  - Van Wagtendonk, W.J., 1946-1951 (Box 13)
  - Veterans Affairs, undated (Box 13)
  - Virus Research in the P3 Lab, 1938 (Box 13)
  - V-Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 13)
  - "W", 1926-1950; (3 folders) (Box 13)
  - W-Z, 1975-1976 (Box 13)
  - Ward (Miscellaneous), 1921-1939 (Box 13)
  - Warren-Miscellaneous, 1923-1937 (Box 13)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1947-1956 (Box 13)
  - Wilding, James L., 1935-1942 (Box 13)
  - Wildlife Research Small Grant Program, 1970-1971 (Box 13)
  - Williams, Elliot C., 1949-1950 (Box 13)
  - Williamson, Edward Bruce, 1927; 1933 (Box 13)
  - Wilson, Ira T., 1923-1946 (Box 13)
  - Winona Lake Biological Station, 1950-1960 (Box 13)
  - Wistar Institute, 1932-1940 (Box 13)
  - Wright-Miscellaneous, 1927-1937 (Box 13)
  - "X, Y, Z", 1917-1957 (Box 13)
  - Young, Frank N. (Box 13)
    - 1944-1954 (Box 13)
    - 1976 (Box 13)
  - Zeiner, Fredrick N., 1950; undated (Box 14)
  - Zoologists, 1942-1948 (Box 14)
  - Zoology (Box 14)
    - Dept, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1965-1967; undated (Box 14)
    - Faculty: Bibliographics, 1969-1972; undated (Box 14)
    - History In Indiana And At IU, undated (Box 14)
    - Newsletter, 1966-1968 (Box 14)
    - Research Newsletters, 1967-1974; undated (Box 14)
    - Staff Meeting Agendas, 1967-1970; undated (Box 14)
  - 100 Level Courses, 1975-1976; undated (Box 14)
    (See Also Ad Hoc Committee on 100 level courses)
  - DBS Executive Committee Notices And Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 14)